[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[reporters speaking Japanese]
[indistinct chatter]
[video games blipping]
Oi. Oh!
[laughs] Aah!
[speaking Japanese]
[chuckles]
[grunts, groans]
- Oi.
Oi.
Oi!
[engine humming]
[engine shuts off]
- Katagiri-san.
- Oh, Jake.
I was hoping if you
have a second to talk
about these yakuza raids.
You are covering
yakuza again?
Well, for this story,
yeah, we all are.
Off the record,
could you just tell me
what they're charging you with?
[speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
The plans you are looking for
will look like this.
The name of the train station
will be here.
He told Claudine he always
keeps them in his home office
to ensure the location
stays secret.
Well, then it's a good thing
he invited me to his house.
He's cooking me dinner.
Samantha.
[speaking Japanese]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[knocking]
[door clicks open]
Yo.
Shh.
[speaking Japanese]
[chuckles]
[shouts]
Oi!
[shouting playfully]
[moans]
[hisses]
Aah!
[groaning]
[exhales heavily]
[speaking Japanese]
Eh?
Hmm.
- [speaking Japanese]
[line beeps]
- Hey.
It's me again.
I'm really sorry
about the other night.
Can you call me back?
[phone beeps]
[speaking Japanese]
[clears throat]
Hmm.
So is it the girl
from the embassy party?
That voicemail you just left,
I'm guessing it's the girl.
You're not a bad reporter,
are you?
[chuckles] I try.
So?
Yeah, it's her.
She's beautiful.
Tin-Tin is sure
he's seen her somewhere
but can't place her.
Hmm.
Well, I'm pretty sure
it's over anyway, so...
Is there any
Japanese context in which
not returning my calls
means anything
besides "go fuck yourself"?
No.
So are you really in the FBI?
[chuckles]
I would love to say yes
to impress you,
but no, I'm with
the State Department.
But your boss is FBI?
- Lynn?
- Yeah.
Yes, but I work with her
but not under her.
I'm just a paper pusher,
facilitate briefings,
that kind of thing.
I can think of worse jobs.
I'm not complaining.
I would have taken any post
to get out of the U.S.
So now that you know,
does that make you
more or less interested
in this drink?
About the same level
of interest.
[lounge music playing
over speakers]
♪ ♪
Is there somewhere
more fun we can go to?
♪ ♪
[upbeat music playing]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
Reminds me of a place
I used to go to in Bethesda.
You're not impressed?
I'm very impressed
and grateful to you
for bringing me.
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[laughs]
Something I said?
We don't discuss
personal matters here.
Work at work,
home at home,
bar at bar.
That doesn't bother you,
dividing yourself up
into pieces like that?
Some pieces fit
in some places.
Some fit in others.
It's just,
I've done the closet.
It almost killed me.
I want to live my life,
all my life,
in the open, you know?
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
- Iya.
[tense music]
[speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
Ma, I told Jess weeks ago,
I got the plane ticket.
Yeah, Joshua,
there's a world of difference
between having a plane ticket
and getting on a plane.
Fair enough.
This party,
this whole thing,
is only gonna matter to him
if you are there.
[phone buzzing]
Mom, I'm waiting
for a call from a lawyer
who could be a source,
so I have to go, OK?
I'm sorry.
Just tell me
that you're coming, please.
I'm coming, I promise. Bye.
[clears throat]
It's me.
We need to meet,
our usual place.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
[laughter]
Erika, you are so good.
You had those guys
eating out of your hands.
Yeah.
It's less
about how good you look
and more
about how well you listen.
- Ooh.
- [speaking Japanese]
[laughter]
So what's up
with you and Sato?
[laughter]
- [speaking Japanese]
[clears throat]
We are just
getting to know each other.
Oh, well,
that's what Samantha said,
and we all know
how that turned out.
Stop.
Don't make her feel bad.
- Oh.
- Samantha is so over him now.
She won't even look at him.
[speaking Japanese]
Wait.
[chuckles]
Samantha and Sato
were together?
Oh.
[laughter]
[chuckles]
Ow!
[indistinct chatter]
- [speaking Japanese]
[classical music playing
over speakers]
♪ ♪
I'm so glad you came.
I'm so sorry
about the other night.
Just listen.
We don't have much time.
He's back.
♪ ♪
Are you OK?
Did he say where he went?
No, but when he left,
he was very ill.
Now he's fine, like a new man.
New, like what?
What does that mean?
Jake, you must
stay away from him.
Yeah, yeah,
I'm done with all that.
Promise me.
I promise.
I am not going back
to my old life.
I will see you soon.
♪ ♪
[crickets chirping,
dog barking]
[phone ringing]
He's back--
Tozawa.
How do you know?
A reliable source
with firsthand knowledge
who also said
that he was ill when he left
and now he's healthy,
like a new man.
- Jake.
- Yes, I know.
I'm not going anywhere
near him.
But did you know
that he was ill?
And where was he?
[sighs]
Until we know that, we wait.
Remember, Jake,
patience is not weakness, huh?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [speaking Japanese]
[exhales heavily]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Hai.
- Hei.
[speaking Japanese]
[both chuckle]
OK, I have everything.
I have everything, OK.
Don't forget
to keep an eye on Kenji.
So it's not a dohan?
No.
Do you like him?
Masa?
I do, but that isn't
what this is.
It's for us, for the club.
Why didn't you ever tell me
about you and Sato?
Should I have?
Wait, are you guys, like--
No.
- Oh.
- I mean, not yet, but...
[chuckles]
Why didn't you tell me?
I should have.
I just--
I'm not sure I can be
with another yakuza.
Hmm.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[both chuckle]
- OK, guess I'd better go.
- Mm-hmm.
- You good?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Have fun.
Thanks.
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[intriguing music]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
[shouts in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[indistinct announcement
over P.A. system]
[laughs]
[grunts]
[speaking Japanese]
[laughs]
Yes.
[shushing]
[engine turning over]
[intriguing music]
♪ ♪
[car door clicks open]
[car door slams]
[gravel crunching]
- Here we are.
- OK. [chuckles]
- Ready?
- Yeah.
OK.
Follow me.
Just here.
Yeah.
[keys jingling]
[chuckles]
Oh, wow!
Ah!
This is beautiful.
Mm.
I'm so glad you came.
I want the tour.
I thought you'd never ask.
This way.
- OK.
After you.
[speaking Japanese]
[both chuckle]
Kitchen is there.
And whenever you need it,
the bathroom
is around the corner.
Bedroom's upstairs?
Mm.
Mm, I'm sure that view
is amazing.
It is.
Unfortunately, I spend
most of my time in here.
Ah.
No view of the ocean.
Actually, there is a view.
[chuckles]
Wow.
[rock music
playing faintly over stereo]
♪ ♪
[music loudens]
[music stops]
[sighs]
[laughter]
[laughs]
[groans]
[mysterious music]
[bag thuds]
♪ ♪
[laughter]
[light music playing
over speakers]
♪ ♪
This is one of my favorite
songs from my time in London.
♪ ♪
♪ Midnight pretenders ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Uneasy heart ♪
All right.
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
Are you a good dancer?
I'm pretty bad.
[chuckles]
♪ How much I love you ♪
♪ I love you ♪
[singing in Japanese]
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
Can I use your bathroom?
Was I that bad?
[both chuckle]
Of course.
I'll finish cooking.
OK.
♪ ♪
♪ Every time I wish ♪
♪ Monopolize your love ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Every time I wish ♪
♪ That you would be mine ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ Midnight pretenders ♪
[knife tapping]
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Secret love ♪
[grunts, sighs]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ Say goodbye ♪
[camera shutter snaps]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
Fuck.
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[both gasp]
- You scared me.
What happened?
My knife skills need work.
Do you have Band-Aids?
Let's grab Band-Aids.
I think so.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Oh.
Looks bad.
[speaking Japanese]
[phone ringing]
- Tin-Tin, it's me.
I need you to look up
this address for me.
And tell me
what this building is.
I'm fine, Jake-san.
Thank you for asking.
Look, I couldn't get through
to anyone at the office.
I'm not near a computer.
Tozawa is back.
Tozawa is back?
Yes, I went
to the Bengoshi Kaikan
to interview
this yakuza lawyer.
And I saw him,
so I followed him.
And now he's in
this building...
OK, OK, I'll call you
right back.
Jake, be careful.
Thank you.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[both speaking Korean]
[water running]
[breathing shakily]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[chuckles softly]
Hmm?
[both chuckle softly]
[suspenseful music]
[camera shutter snapping]
♪ ♪
Where'd you learn
to cook like that?
In London.
I studied architecture there
many years ago.
I was so homesick,
so I started cooking for myself
to make home feel closer.
That's nice.
Are you ever homesick?
No.
Where are you from
that you don't miss it?
Utah.
Utah?
Yeah.
I wanted more from my life.
Hmm.
I wanted more from my life too.
[singing in Japanese]
So do you have anyone?
You mean
like wife and kids?
Yeah.
Now would be the time
to tell me.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
No.
It's just me and my work.
- Yeah?
- Mm.
Me too.
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
[engine revving]
[speaking Japanese]
Are you kidding me?
♪ ♪
Fuck.
[speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
[laughs]
[grunting rhythmically]
[shouts]
- [laughs]
[tense music]
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
[laughter]
[zipper scratches]
- [grunts]
[urine trickling]
♪ ♪
[groans]
[groaning]
♪ ♪
[screams]
[groans]
I'm sorry that you have
to drive me all the way home.
I'm not.
I'll take all the time
with you that I can get.
[both chuckle]
Oh, my car keys.
Be right back.
Samantha.
Yeah?
Did you go through my bag?
What?
What were you
looking for, Samantha?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[wheezing]
Oi. Oi!
♪ ♪
[wheezing]
[speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
[groans]
[knife clatters]
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
[grunts, chuckles]
[shouting]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[chuckles]